{
    "id": "72df58a28e4749c196d1a71183ad021d",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car suffered heavy damage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "car",
                "heavy",
                "damage"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35c1b8c4c51b47338c8ab841aa836509"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every dog has his day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "dog",
                "day"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1fbfe3fa034143eb92adc7dea693f693"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought enough sugar.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "enough",
                "sugar"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16c64f4047d34ba8b004d5bbf48b51f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was wearing a blue gown.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wearing",
                "blue",
                "gown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1516ce2c5184c6da2ac7f3075fc7e9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have had my fair share of disappointments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "fair",
                "disappointments"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "818fa961ca8643f7bef4782d8b3b32e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The way was long and the wind was cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "way",
                "long",
                "wind"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eb1eed373d7f4f2d91d811c76ccf7afd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Donâ€™t cry over spilt milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cry",
                "over",
                "spilt"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "662774f8308a461eaef2973d928e93ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "He won the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "first",
                "prize"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d18fd3fa76d434192b994d9733b7636"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a man of few words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "man",
                "of",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a833e533b13849a39f35b785d15770e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He died a glorious death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "glorious",
                "death"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48c570967fdb4c93b934f4b98bacdbf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "A small leak can sink a great ship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leak",
                "sink",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "59bef0f80e574c9fa247649829151708"
        },
        {
            "question": "King Francis was a hearty king and loved a royal sport.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearty",
                "and",
                "sport"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f038cbaaf4649eab944b3c535674b52"
        }
    ]
}